<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AgileSyndro.me</title>
    <link>https://blog.agilesyndro.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AgileSyndro.me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.agilesyndro.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>13 Years later, and &#39;How was your day?&#39; still terrifies both of us.</title>
      <link>https://blog.agilesyndro.me/posts/how-was-your-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 06:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.agilesyndro.me/posts/how-was-your-day/</guid>
      <description>13 Years Today is my 13th wedding anniversary. Let me start by saying my wife is amazing. Like, I could make all of you jealous by talking about how awesome she is. After 4,748 days of marriage though, the one question that still terrifies both of us is when she asks, &amp;ldquo;How was your day at work?&amp;rdquo; It goes one of two ways:
 I was successful in getting Packer to trigger some Ansible code that built an AMI that subsequently launched Terraform, all of which initiated from a GitHub Pull Request monitored by Jenkins AND Concourse!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened during the maintenance window...</title>
      <link>https://blog.agilesyndro.me/posts/during-the-maintenance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 19:20:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.agilesyndro.me/posts/during-the-maintenance/</guid>
      <description>Epic Migration It was one of those once-a-year crazy maintenance weekends. You know the kind where we&amp;rsquo;ve got to take the whole stack down for a weekend while we migrate half a billion records from an old system to a shiny new one. The kind where nobody wants to discuss the rollback strategy because it&amp;rsquo;s as ugly as the upgrade. Let me say a million things went right during this migration, and it goes down in the books as an epic success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terraform Modules Suck, but you should still use them</title>
      <link>https://blog.agilesyndro.me/posts/terraform-modules-suck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 19:02:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.agilesyndro.me/posts/terraform-modules-suck/</guid>
      <description>Terraform Like so many other people I jumped into Terraform right away. This was the answer I was looking for. It could provide an automated way to store AWS configurations in source control. It also let me try out Azure, Google, and many other providers in a cloud-agnostic (sorta) kinda of way.
Within a few days there were segments of code everywhere to create an EC2 instance. Everybody on my team made their own Terraform code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1998 is calling, and it wants a website</title>
      <link>https://blog.agilesyndro.me/posts/1998-is-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 10:28:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.agilesyndro.me/posts/1998-is-calling/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s 1998 and the local robotics club wants a website. You&amp;rsquo;ve got this, you know HTML, some simple JavaScript and how to use Windows Paint to re-size images. The website design isn&amp;rsquo;t the problem, it never really is. Now comes the hard part, let&amp;rsquo;s get our web server up and running:
 Red Hat 5.2 Apache v1.3 DNS A Record FTP Server for transfering the files  But let&amp;rsquo;s not forget what you had to tell the team:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>